Patryk Ptasiński

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Personal Data

PLACE OF BIRTH: Warsaw, Poland

Age: 27 years old

PHONE: (+48) 510 355 151 EMAIL: resume@ipepe.pl HOMEPAGE: www.ipepe.pl

GITHUB: @ipepe

Summary

Educated and experienced software engineer with broad knowledge in the field of computer science. Working in IT for almost 10 years and interested in computers since childhood. Worked with wide range of technologies and architectures like desktop, mobile and web applications.

WORK EXPERIENCE - PART I

2019- | Senior Ruby on Rails Developer at Visuality

Responsible for building applications in high quality oriented software house. Working in very organized teams with Engineering Managers and Project Managers for many clients and projects.

Full Stack development: Ruby on Rails, React, PostgreSQL, Redis and Elasticsearch. Related: AWS, Heroku, Github and Brakeman

2018- WebGL, React and Ruby Developer/Azure Cloud Architect at Skriware

Responsible for creating advanced Three.js based online CAD editor. Also did monitoring and full stack development for Rails application related to 3D Printing and IOT Devices. Built from ground up Azure infrastructure spanning 8 VM and 30+ containers

Full Stack development: Three.js, Ruby on Rails, React, NodeJS, ActionCable, PostgreSQL and Redis.

Related: Azure, Capistrano, MicroServices, Integration, AirBrake (Errbit), Monitoring and GitLab.

2017 | Lead Ruby Developer at **DAFTCODE SP. Z O.O.**

Responsible for planning, estimating and distributing work in a team, architecture and quality of code for medium Rails application that contained market of models prepared to be 3D printed.

Full Stack development: Bootstrap, Ruby on Rails, PostgreSQL, Redis and Elastic-search.

Related: Kanbanery, Capistrano, Integration, AirBrake (Errbit), Monitoring and GitLab

2015-2016 | Lead Ruby Developer at In4mates sp. z o.o. sp.k.

Lead developer in a big project related to the accounting and business processes. Managed team of 5 developers. Responsible for architecture, maintenance, deployment - whole system development life cycle.

Full Stack development: Bootstrap, EmberJS, Ruby on Rails, PostgreSQL and more. Related: Jenkins, Redmine, Capistrano, Docker, Vagrant, Integration, Monitoring and GitLab

2012-2014 Systems Administrator and T2 Helpdesk at Operator Gazociągów Przesyłowych GAZ-SYSTEM S.A.

Performed second level on-site Helpdesk. Administrator of packages, applications and compliance for SCCM (2500 workstations) and on-site Active Directory management (600 users and computers).

Related: DevOps, Zabbix, PowerShell, VBScript, Acronis, Hardware Inventory, SLA, Microsoft Deployment Toolkit.

ORK EXP.

Work Experience - Part II

2012 24x7 Helpline Support at Digital Virgo SA

> Responsible for supporting Paid SMS Gateway and part-time Helpdesk Support. Related: DevOps, SLA, Linux, Nagios, Scripting, Hardware Inventory and Software Lincesing.

2011 Outsourced Systems Administrator and Helpdesk at Synergia Polska

Responsible for the infrastructure of multiple client companies. Developed multiple small tools and applications in Java and C-Sharp. Related: SLA, Monitoring, VNC, DevOps, Hardware and Software Technical Support.

2010 OpenERP Developer and Helpdesk Support at LACAN Technologies

Created multiple OpenERP modules. Performed duties as Secondary Systems Administrator and resolved Helpdesk tickets. Related: SLA, DevOps, Spiceworks, Monitoring, VNC, Python and MySQL.

Education

2012-2017 Engineer degree in The Faculty of Information Technology,

Polish-Japanese Academy Of Information Technology

Part time studies | Speciality: Networks of Mobile Devices Thesis: "Urban navigation based on WIFI location data"

Advisor: dr. inż. Michał Tomaszewski

Related: Ruby On Rails, Big data, WIFI, Android, Geolocation, Post-

GIS

2008-2011 Secondary Education,

Academic High School under supervision of Polish-Japanese

Academy Of Information Technology

Speciality: Information Technology

Related: Java, SQL, UML

LANGUAGES

Polish: Mothertongue

ENGLISH: Fluent Japaneese: Beginner

Computer Skills

Arduino, Raspberry PI, Electronics, PCB making, iOS Development, Basic:

FDM 3D Printing, 3D Modelling, AI and Data Science

Intermediate: Linux - Ubuntu/Debian Family, Git, Local Network Configuration for

> Windows and Linux, Network File Sharing and Backup, Android Development, Web Crawling, Reverse Engineering and GameDev

Advanced: Ruby on Rails, JavaScript(Browser and NodeJS) and PostgreSQL

Interests and Activities

Published multiple opensource projects and libraries. Hacktoberfest Participant and unofficial ambassador. Indie games developer. Cars and motorcycles enthusiast. Currently exploring 3D Printing combined with microcontrollers and single board computers in areas like IoT, robotics and automation.

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in my application to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment process under the Personal Data Protection Act as of 29 August 1997, consolidated text: Journal of Laws 2016, item 922 as amended.